We're going to work on the practice of the face, which in the osteopathic concept, is a holistic concept.
我们将进行面部实践工作，在整骨疗法概念中，这是一个
holistic.
整体概念。
It means that we take not only zone A, B, C and D, I use the environment
这意味着我们不仅关注区域A、B、C和D，我还利用我周围的
around me.
环境。
It's almost this environment that reorganizes me, you understand, since I am dependent on this
几乎是这个环境重塑了我，你明白吗？因为我依赖于这个
All this reading that we are going to do at the level of the face, of the nails, in fact, it is an indirect reflection
我们将在面部、指甲上进行的所有解读，实际上，都是间接反映了
indirectly towards...
...
of the neural crest. This means that the neural crest is a tissue that is at the same time
神经嵴。这意味着神经嵴是一种组织，它既是
informer,
信息传递者，
so it receives information, but through this almost arachnoid network that
因此它接收信息，但通过它在身体中几乎是蛛网膜状的
it has in the body,
网络，
which is found a bit in areas on the peripheral plane, on the visceral plane. That is
这在周边区域和内脏区域都有所体现。也就是说，面部是内在的表达，面部也向内在传递信息。
to say that the face is the expression of the interior and the face informs the interior.
也就是说，面部是内在的表达，面部也向内在传递信息。
When we see the
当我们看到
mandibular arches, that is, at the moment when the embryo...
下颌弓时，也就是说，当胚胎...
will form this flexion, there will be what we call branchial pouches
将形成这种屈曲时，将会有我们所说的鳃囊，它们将是
will be
将是
lines of force on an almost cartilaginous plane
在几乎是软骨或中胚层平面上的力线，它们将朝向我的颅底
or mesodermal that will orient towards my base
或中胚层平面上的力线，它们将朝向我的颅底
of the skull, which means that this base of the skull receives a convergence of
这意味着颅底接收到面部信息的汇聚，
facial information
面部信息的汇聚，
direct vis-à-vis of both my
直接与我的
bronchial and the wrapping of my brain. It's a crossroads of
支气管和我的大脑包膜相关。这是一个信息交汇点，它将
information that will be
信息交汇点，它将
reflected on a glandular, circulatory,
影响腺体、循环、
lymphatic and even on a neurological axis.
淋巴，甚至神经轴。所以请记住，颅底不仅是
skull is a balance
我的神经颅和内脏颅之间的平衡，而且所有信息...
is given, it gives us the lines of force of the practice and we will see how we can rebalance
都已给出，这为我们提供了实践的力线，我们将看到如何在张力层面上，在整骨疗法层面上重新平衡蝶枕结合。
finally on a tensional level on the osteopathic level the sphenobasilar symphysis
最终在张力层面上，在整骨疗法层面上重新平衡蝶枕结合。
by
相对于此，它只是寻求最佳适应。甲状腺功能不佳会导致活动受限，请记住，这始终是“我能接受”
does not
不
function well, it gives hypomobility, don't forget, it's always I know
功能不佳会导致活动受限，请记住，这始终是“我能接受”
to take
和“我必须能够给予”。那些充血的人是那些不给予的人。
that will really organize this level, and the whole face, it's a dynamic movement
这将真正组织这个层面，而整个面部，是我大脑在发展中的
dynamic movement of my brain, in development.
动态运动。
This means that initially, I have a prosencephalon, so the most anterior part
这意味着，一开始，我有一个前脑，也就是我大脑最
anterior part of my brain,
前端的部分，
my encephalons, rhombencephalons, and then I have what is called the
我的脑，菱脑，然后我有所谓的
spinal canal,
脊髓管，
and it is essentially the prosencephalon that will give a dynamic movement,
而主要是前脑会产生动态运动，
two small lateral balls that will "hypertrophy"
两个小的侧向球会“过度生长”
and which will make a movement like this of
并会像这样进行
development. It will grow and at some point there is a brake in front, it will create
发育运动。它会生长，在某个时刻，前面会有一个阻碍，这会形成
a
一个
specific field to form the frontal and then it will make such a movement of development like
特定的区域来形成额叶，然后它会像这样、这样、这样、这样进行发育运动，
this, like this, like this, like this, to form
以形成
a hemisphere on the left and on the right. In this phase,
左半球和右半球。在这个阶段，
a phase of facial straightening
是面部矫正的阶段
and that's where initially
正是在这里，最初
my face which was compressed
我的脸被压缩了
we could say practically
我们可以说几乎是
between my heart and my brain
在我的心脏和大脑之间
will suddenly open up in this space
会突然在这个空间中打开
and that's how
就是这样
that the lateral zones like the
侧面区域，例如
optic placode
视板
here which was quite lateral
这里原本相当靠外侧
will come to integrate forward
会向前整合
like the nasal placode which is quite
就像鼻板一样，它相当
lateral will come to integrate towards the midline
靠外侧，会向中线整合
and that's where you have
正是在这里，您会看到
all this median line that forms on the anterior part,
所有这些中线都在前部形成，
which is ultimately a median line of anticipation.
这最终是一条预期的中线。
You have a whole zone of anticipation, of probability.
您有一个完整的预期区域，一个可能性区域。
I have here this whole phase of integration like that,
我在这里有整个整合阶段，就像这样，
which is called the neural crest flow.
我们称之为神经嵴的流动。
That is, from the posterior mesencephalon,
也就是说，从后中脑，
rhombomere,
菱脑节，
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, which completely, like that, invades,
1、2、3、4、5、6、7，它会完全像这样侵入，
integrates the mesoderm to form mesectoderm,
整合中胚层以形成中外胚层，
which is called the neural crest flow.
我们称之为神经嵴的流动。
And which will completely invade the whole face, all this area, at
它会完全侵入整个面部，整个这个区域，在
the level of the visceral system, up to here.
内脏系统层面，直到这里。
It's really a flow, like that.
它真的是一个流动，就像这样。
At the same time, I have this movement of development of my brain.
同时，我的大脑也在进行这种发育运动。
At the same time, I have all these dural sheaths organizing here, like this, you
与此同时，我所有的硬脑膜鞘都在这里组织起来，就像这样，你
see.
看。
And at the same time, my entire anterior line is gradually forming.
与此同时，我的整个前线也正在一点一点地形成。
So here, I have drawn in orange the entire area from the surface
所以在这里，我用橙色画出了从表面到深度的整个区域。
to the depth.
到深处。
This is what we call the mesectoderm.
这就是我们所说的中胚层。
Skin, here, it's not the same thing.
皮肤，这里，不是一回事。
It's a part of the muscles, the bones, etc.
它是肌肉、骨骼等的一部分。
The cornea, yellow ones like that at the level of the water.
角膜，像这样在水中的黄色。
the eye, etc. are an integration.
眼睛等都是一种整合。